Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Business Papers, 1938-1992 (Box 439-440, 533-535, 551-591, 623-624, 635, 768-769, 774-775, 793, Mapcase folder 3-4)
  - Danny Kaye Productions, 1952-1986
    - Dena Pictures Files, 1952-1986
      - Danny Kaye Show, 1962-1973
        Contracts; financial reports; production materials including music clearance sheets, show rundowns, rehearsal schedules, and staff lists; and invoices and paid bills. Production stills can be found in the Photographs series.
        Arranged in four file units: Contracts, Financial Materials, Production Material, and Paid Bills.
        - Employment Contracts, 1963-1966, Contracts with program dancers, musicians, and production staff. (Box-folder 571/1-572/7)
        - General Contracts, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 572/8-10)
        - Guest Contracts, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 572/9-574/65)
        - Financial Reports – Domestic, 1963-1967, Includes correspondence, invoices, below-the-line production estimates and overrun requests, labor utilization reports, and pension remittances. (Box-folder 575/1-577/1)
        - Financial Reports – Foreign Runs, 1963-1972, Includes correspondence, distribution agreements, payments received and made, and record of film transmittal. (Box-folder 577/2-23)
        - Financial Reports – Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 577/24)
        - CBS Invoice and Payment, 1963 (Box-folder 578/1)
        - CBS Official Notice Re: Delivery/Invoices 1963-1967 (Box-folder 578/2)
        - Color Test, July 20, 1965 (Box-folder 578/3)
        - Contact Lists, undated (Box-folder 578/4)
        - Copyrights, undated (Box-folder 440/5)
        - Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 578/5-6)
        - Fan Mail Evaluation, 1967 (Box-folder 578/7)
        - "Giovanni" Sketches/Lists of Clips, undated (Box-folder 578/8)
        - Master Schedule of Domestic Re-Use and Foreign Residuals Paid, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 578/9)
        - Miscellaneous, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 578/10)
        - Music Clearance Sheets, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 578/11-14)
        - Music Management, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 578/15-17)
        - Print Requests, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 578/18)
        - Production Information, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 578/19-21)
        - Publicity, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 578/22, 625/5)
        - Show Notebooks, 1963-1967, Includes booking slips, contracts, fan mail reports, foreign payments, ratings, records of payment, schedules, and staff lists (Box-folder 578/23-27)
        - Show Rundown, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 578/28)
        - Show Summaries, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 578/29)
        - Paid Bills, 1964-1966, Includes check copies, invoices, and purchase orders (Box-folder 579/1-581/40)
      - John Gary Show, 1965-1967
        Contracts; financial reports; production materials, including music clearance sheets, show rundowns, rehearsal schedules, and staff lists; and invoices and paid bills.
        Arranged in five file units: Contracts, Financial Materials, Production Material, Invoices, and Correespondence.
        - Employment Contracts, 1966 (Box-folder 582/1-28)
        - Guest Contracts, 1966 (Box-folder 582/29-64)
        - Financial Reports, 1966 (Box-folder 582/65-66)
        - Production Materials, 1966 (Box-folder 582/67-78, 583/1-3)
        - Invoices, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 583/4-43)
        - Correspondence
          - Bonis, Herb, 1966 (Box-folder 583/44-45)
          - Csida, Joseph, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 583/46)
          - John Gary Fan Club, 1967 (Box-folder 583/47)
  - Sylvia Fine Files, 1946-1992
    Materials documenting Sylvia Fines' activities as a teacher, composer, and producer. These include correspondence, budgets, clippings, contracts, invoices, lecture notes and transcripts, license agreements, notes and research material, photographs and slides, program treatments, proposals, scripts, student files, and papers.
    Arranged in two sub-subseries: Miscellaneous Files and Musical Comedy Tonight.
    - Miscellaneous Files, 1946-1992
      Correspondence, program treatments, lecture notes and transcripts, student files and papers, and contracts.
      Alphabetically by folder title.
      - 92nd Street YMHA Lyricists Series Performance, 1975-1976, Correspondents include Jackie Onassis. (Box-folder 584/1)
      - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, 1952-1958 (Box-folder 584/2)
      - American Guild of Authors and Composers/Screenwriters' Protective Association, 1951-1959 (Box-folder 584/3)
      - American Society of Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1955-1959, 1971 (Box-folder 584/4)
      - American Society of Authors and Publishers (ASCAP) - Music Rights, undated (Box-folder 793/7)
      - Annenberg, Walter, 1957 (Box-folder 584/5)
      - Article Drafts, undated (Box-folder 584/6)
      - Aspen Institute, 1978 (Box-folder 584/7)
      - The Authors League of America, Inc., 1953-1958 (Box-folder 584/8)
      - Awards, 1952-1953, 1962, 1986-1988, Includes photograph of Sylvia Fine. (Box-folder 584/9)
      - Beginner Books, Inc., 1957, Correspondents include Phyllis Cerf. (Box-folder 584/10)
      - Beverly Hills Hadassah/Woman of Achievement, 1983 (Box-folder 584/11)
      - Book Contracts, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 584/12)
      - Bricker, Seymour, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 584/13)
      - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 584/14)
      - Brooklyn College, 1957-1958, 1982, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 584/15-20)
      - Center for Learning through the Dance, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 584/21)
      - Composers Guild of America, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 584/22)
      - Correspondence, 1946, 1952, 1957-1976, 1980-1986, 1990, Correspondents include Kermit Boomgarden, John Brademas, Jimmy Carter, Phyllis Cerf, Margot Fonteyn, and Jacob Javits. (Box-folder 584/23-27)
      - The Day of the Turtle, 1967-1968, see also We're a Whole New Thing. (Box-folder 584/28)
      - Dayan, Yãel, 1962, Correspondents include Ivan Lengyel and Moshe Pearlman. (Box-folder 584/29)
      - Development Projects, 1959-1960, 1966, 1968, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 584/30)
      - Doctor's Dilemma, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 584/31)
      - Eleanor Roossevelt Memorial Foundation, 1963-1965, Correspondents include Hubert Humphrey and Adlai Stevenson. (Box-folder 584/32)
      - Fine, Sylvia, Miscellaneous, 1954-1958, undated (Box-folder 584/33)
      - Fine, Sylvia - Name, 1956 (Box-folder 793/8)
      - Fine, Sylvia, Programs/Music, 1937, undated, Includes "Oh, it's for Brooklyn" by Sylvia Fine Kaye. (Box-folder 584/34)
      - Flekman, Manny, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 585/1)
      - Fred Allen Memorial, 1963 (Box-folder 585/2)
      - Gibson, Dunn & Crutcher, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 585/3)
      - Helping Hand Mother of the Year, 1982 (Box-folder 585/4)
      - Hunter College – Kaye Theatre, 1986-1991, Correspondents include Sol Linowitz, Hal Prince, and Donna Shalala. (Box-folder 585/5-9)
      - Johns Hopkins University Lecture/Fine and Danny, 1986 (Box-folder 585/10-14)
      - Kaye, Dena, 1990, Includes photograph of Dena Kaye. (Box-folder 585/15)
      - Lorenz Hart Tribute, 1973 (Box-folder 585/16)
      - McMahon, Kirk, 1986, Includes photographs. (Box-folder 585/17)
      - Metropolitan Opera Subscription, 1966 (Box-folder 585/18)
      - Morgan, Len, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 585/19)
      - Musical Comedy Library Project, 1975, undated (Box-folder 585/20)
      - Popo the Puppet Sheet Music Cover, undated (Box-folder 624/6)
      - Ratner, Victor M., 1949-1963 (Box-folder 585/21-23, 769/8)
      - RCA Victor Popular Album Club, 1959 (Box-folder 585/24)
      - Requests for Use of Material, 1965, 1990 (Box-folder 585/25)
      - Royalties, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 585/26)
      - San Francisco Toy Museum, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 585/27)
      - The Scarlet Pimpernel, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 585/28)
      - Syndicated Column Project, 1957 (Box-folder 794/1)
      - Song Titles, undated (Box-folder 585/29)
      - UNICEF, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 585/30-32)
      - USC Course, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 585/33-34, 586/1-12)
      - USC Lorenz Hart Tribute Show, 1973 (Box-folder 794/2/)
      - USO Christmas Show, 1958 (Box-folder 586/13)
      - WAIF Program Book, 1963 (Box-folder 586/14)
      - We're a Whole New Thing, 1967-1968, undated, see also The Day of the Turtle. (Box-folder 586/15-17)
      - White House Conference on the Arts – Congressional Hearing, 1977, Correspondents include John Brademas. (Box-folder 586/18)
      - Wilson, Jack, 1967 (Box-folder 586/19)
      - Yale University Seminar, 1973-1976, Correspondents include Paul Rudnick and Wendy Wasserstein. (Box-folder 586/20-22)
    - Musical Comedy Tonight, 1975-1989
      Correspondence, proposals, budgets, invoices, scripts, notes and research material, license agreements, clippings, photographs, and slides.
      Arranged by file unit, with general Musical Comedy Tonight material first, followed by material related to each of the three programs. Materials are arranged alphabetically by folder title within each file unit.
      - Musical Comedy Tonight
        - Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 586/23-26, 587/1-11)
        - Rights, Grand and Performing, 1977-1982, undated (Box-folder 587/12-15)
        - Rights, License Agreements, 1976-1977, 1980, 1986, undated (Box-folder 587/16-18)
        - Rights, Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 587/19)
        - Research – Correspondence and Reports, undated (Box-folder 587/20-21)
        - Research – Fine, Sylvia Notes, undated, Includes Words and Music: A Book of Burlesques by Sigmund Spaeth; inscribed to Fine from her father. (Box-folder 588/1)
        - Research – Musical Reviews, 1938-1970 (Box-folder 588/2)
        - Research – Musicals, 1917-1969 (Box-folder 588/3-4)
        - Research – Musical Comedy Library Listed by Show, undated (Box-folder 588/5-7)
        - Research – Recording Index, undated (Box 774-775)
        - Slides
          - Description List, undated (Box-folder 533/1)
          - Annie Get Your Gun, undated (Box-folder 533/2)
          - Anything Goes, undated (Box-folder 533/3)
          - As Thousands Cheer, undated (Box-folder 533/4)
          - Irving Berlin, undated (Box-folder 533/5)
          - Black Crook, undated (Box-folder 533/6)
          - Boys From Syracuse, undated (Box-folder 533/7)
          - Cartier, undated (Box-folder 533/8)
          - A Connecticut Yankee, undated (Box-folder 533/9)
          - Finian's Rainbow, undated (Box-folder 533/10)
          - Garrick Gaieties, undated (Box-folder 533/11)
          - Good News, undated (Box-folder 533/12)
          - Hit the Deck, undated (Box-folder 533/13)
          - Jubilee, undated (Box-folder 533/14)
          - Jerome Kern, undated (Box-folder 533/15)
          - Kiss Me, Kate, undated (Box-folder 533/16)
          - Lady Be Good, undated (Box-folder 533/17)
          - Lady in the Dark, undated (Box-folder 533/18)
          - Leave it to Jane, undated (Box-folder 533/19)
          - The Man who Came to Dinner, undated (Box-folder 533/20)
          - The Mikado, undated (Box-folder 533/21)
          - Musical Comedy Tonight Series, undated (Box-folder 533/22-23)
          - Of Thee I Sing, undated (Box-folder 533/24)
          - Oh Boy, undated (Box-folder 533/25)
          - Oklahoma, undated (Box-folder 533/26)
          - Once in a Lifetime, undated (Box-folder 533/27)
          - Pal Joey, undated (Box-folder 533/28)
          - Perils of Pauline, undated (Box-folder 533/29)
          - Pinafore, undated (Box-folder 533/30)
          - Pins and Needles, undated (Box-folder 533/31)
          - Show Boat, undated (Box-folder 533/32)
          - South Pacific, undated (Box-folder 533/33)
          - Sweet Charity, undated (Box-folder 534/1)
          - War Songs, undated (Box-folder 534/2)
          - Webber & Fields, undated (Box-folder 534/3)
          - Writers, undated (Box-folder 534/4)
          - Ziegfeld Follies, undated (Box-folder 534/5)
          - Ziegfeld Theatre, undated (Box-folder 534/6)
          - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 534/7)
      - Musical Comedy Tonight I
        - Budgets, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 588/8)
        - Cast and Crew, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 588/9)
        - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 588/10)
        - Correspondence – Congratulatory A-F, 1979-1980, Correspondents include Steve Allen, Jules Bass, Irving Berlin, Marie Briehl, David Brown, Carol Burnett, Warren Caro, Kyle Cittadin, Robert Clary, Douglas Schoolfield Cramer, Agnes de Mille, Kirk Douglas, Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., and Max Forseter. (Box-folder 588/11)
        - Correspondence – Congratulatory G-L, 1979-1981, Correspondents include Katharine Graham, William Hammerstein, Alan Handley, Helen Hayes, Dolores Hope, Ross Hunter, Saul Ilson, Alfred Knopf, Jr., Perry Lafferty, Harvey A. Leve, Lester S. Levy, Max Liebman, Cynthia Lindsey, Sol Linowitz, Joshua Logan, and Allen Ludden. (Box-folder 588/12)
        - Correspondence – Congratulatory M-R, 1979-1980, Correspondents include Frank McCarthy, William Paley, Hal Prince, Allen Rivkin, Flora Roberts, and Dorothy Rodgers. (Box-folder 588/13)
        - Correspondence – Congratulatory S-Z, 1979-1980, Correspondents include Dore Schary, Eric Sevareid, David Shaw, Dinah Shore, Beverly Sills, Harold Silverman, Lester Smith, Aubrey Solomon, Dennis Stanfill, Hunt Stromburg, Jr., Jean Taxin, Thomas Thompson, Bernard Tillis, Norman Twain, Theodore Voss, Barbara Walters, L. Arnold Weissberg, and Max Wilk. (Box-folder 588/14)
        - Correspondence – Thank You Letters, 1979, Correspondents include Marie Briehl, Helen Gurley Brown, Clifford Campion, Agnes de Mille, Sandy Duncan, Robert McElwaine, Betty Furness, Maria Janis (Mrs. Byron), Sol Linowitz, Lee Radziwill, Abraham Ribicoff, Ruth Rabb, and Bernard Tillis. (Box-folder 588/15)
        - Cost Breakdown Post Production Talent, 1979 (Box-folder 588/16)
        - Credits, 1979 (Box-folder 588/17)
        - Dancers, undated (Box-folder 588/18)
        - Editing Notes, 1979, March-July (Box-folder 588/19)
        - Fundraising, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 588/20)
        - George Foster Peabody Award, 1980, April-May, Correspondents include David Brown, Richard Chamberlain, Frank McCarthy, Philip F. Nelson, Flora Roberts, Dorothy Rodgers, and Stephen Sondheim. (Box-folder 588/21)
        - KCET Expense Reports, 1979, June 25 (Box-folder 588/22)
        - Miscellaneous, 1979, undated (Box-folder 588/23)
        - PBS Station Manager Luncheon, 1979 (Box-folder 588/24)
        - Press, 1979 (Box-folder 588/25-26)
        - Production Material, 1979 (Box-folder 589/1)
        - Publicity, 1979 (Box-folder 589/2)
        - Rights, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 589/3)
        - Rundowns, 1979, January (Box-folder 589/4)
        - Scripts, 1978-1979, undated (Box-folder 589/5-13)
        - Union Agreements, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 589/14)
        - Wilshire Ebell Theatre, 1979 (Box-folder 769/9)
      - Musical Comedy Tonight II
        - Agreements, 1980-1982, Also includes Musical Comedy Tonight III agreements. (Box-folder 589/15)
        - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 589/16)
        - Cast Lists, 1980 (Box-folder 589/17)
        - Credits, 1981 (Box-folder 589/18)
        - Expenses, 1981, undated (Box-folder 589/19)
        - Fan Mail Answered, 1981, Correspondents include Larry Auerbach, Johnny Green, June Tauber Golden, Alfred Knopf, Jr., James Levine, Josh Logan, Nedda Logan, Roddy McDowall, Max Rabb, Lynn Redgrave, Jolene Schlatter, Harold Silverman, Jerry Silverman, and Max Wilk. (Box-folder 589/20)
        - Haber Syndication, 1981 (Box-folder 589/21)
        - Images
          - Description List, undated (Box-folder 535/1)
          - Introduction with Photo Insertion, undated (Box-folder 535/2)
          - Publicity/W. C. Fields and Will Rogers, undated (Box-folder 535/3)
          - Fanny Brice, undated (Box-folder 535/4)
          - Composers and Lyricists, undated (Box-folder 535/5)
          - Oscar Hammerstein II, undated (Box-folder 535/6)
          - E. Y. Harburg, undated (Box-folder 535/7)
          - Lady in the Dark, undated (Box-folder 535/8)
          - Pal Joey, undated (Box-folder 535/9)
          - Richard Rodgers, undated (Box-folder 535/10)
          - Rodgers and Hammerstein, undated (Box-folder 535/11)
          - South Pacific, undated (Box-folder 535/12-13)
          - Sweet Charity, undated (Box-folder 535/14)
        - Insurance, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 589/22)
        - Invoices, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 589/23-24)
        - KCET Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 589/25)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 589/26)
        - Music Cue Sheets, undated (Box-folder 589/27)
        - Payroll, 1980 (Box-folder 589/28)
        - Post Production, 1981 (Box-folder 589/29)
        - Press, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 589/30)
        - Publicity, 1980 (Box-folder 589/31)
        - Rehearsal Schedule, 1980 (Box-folder 590/1)
        - Research Materials, 1980 (Box-folder 590/2)
        - Rights, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 590/3)
        - Scripts, 1980, undated (Box-folder 590/4-8)
        - Set Designs, 1980, undated (Mapcase folder 4)
        - Tams-Witmark Music Library, 1980 (Box-folder 590/9)
        - Timing (Rundown), 1980 (Box-folder 590/10)
        - Wilshire-Ebell Theatre, 1980 (Box-folder 590/11)
      - Musical Comedy Tonight III
        - Accounting, 1983 (Box-folder 590/12)
        - Agreements, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 590/13-15)
        - Beverly Wilshire Hotel, 1985 (Box-folder 590/16)
        - Budget, 1981, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 590/17-18)
        - Casting, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 590/19-20)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 590/21)
        - Correspondence – Fan Letters, 1985, Correspondents include Wallis Annenberg, Marie Breihl, Helen Gurley Brown, Agnes de Mille, Harry Ellis Dickson, Nanette Fabray, Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Johnny Green, Florence Henderson, Swifty Lazar, Sol Linowitz, Josh Logan, Nedda Logan, Frank McCarthy, Tehmi Mehta, Hal Prince, Dorothy Rodgers, George Schlatter, Benay Venuta, and Eli Wallach. (Box-folder 590/22)
        - Correspondence – Thank You Notes, 1985, Correspondents include Anna Bing Arnold, Clifford Campion, Florence Henderson, Roberta Peters, and Clive Revil. (Box-folder 590/23)
        - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1985, Includes photograph of Patti LaBelle with Dance Theatre of Harlem. (Box-folder 590/24)
        - Editing, undated (Box-folder 590/25-30)
        - Fundraising, 1983-1985, undated (Box-folder 590/31-34, 591/1)
        - Hertfelder, Suzanne Working Binder, 1985 (Box-folder 591/2-3)
        - Huntington Hartford Theatre Seating, 1981 (Box-folder 591/4)
        - Insurance, 1985 (Box-folder 591/5)
        - Invoices, 1985 (Box-folder 591/6)
        - Materials Loaned Out, undated (Box-folder 591/7)
        - Materials Received, 1981 (Box-folder 591/8)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 591/9)
        - Monies to Cancel Show, 1982 (Box-folder 591/10)
        - Music Clearances/Music Cues, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 591/11)
        - Musical Numbers, undated (Box-folder 591/12)
        - Musicians, 1985 (Box-folder 591/13)
        - Press, 1985 (Box-folder 591/14)
        - Publicity, 1985, Correspondents include Ann Landers. (Box-folder 591/15)
        - Request for Permission to Use Material, 1986, 1989 (Box-folder 591/16)
        - Research, 1984 (Box-folder 591/17)
        - Resumes, 1980s (Box-folder 591/18)
        - Retake Shoot, 1985, June-July (Box-folder 591/19)
        - Rights, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 591/20-21)
        - Scripts, 1981, 1985, undated (Box-folder 591/22-32)
        - Staff List, 1985 (Box-folder 591/33)
        - Stan Harris Dispute, 1985 (Box-folder 591/34)
        - Texaco, 1983 (Box-folder 591/35)
        - USC Party, 1985, November 14 (Box-folder 591/36)
        - Wilshire-Ebell Theatre, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 591/37)
- Photographs, 1918-1991 (Box 428-430, 435-438, 502-532, 538-541, 622, 625, 627-628, 638-640, 766, 768-769, 787, 791, Mapcase folder 2)
  Images (albums, photographic prints, negatives, transparencies, and slides) documenting Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine's careers and personal lives. Material on Kaye comprises the bulk of the series. Additional images are located throughout the collection and indicated in the container list wherever possible.
  Organized as two subseries. Loose photographs cover all aspects of Kaye's career and include portraits, publicity shots, and production stills from The Danny Kaye Show and his films. Also included are Kaye, Kaminsky, and Fine family photographs and images relating to Kaye's hobbies. Albums document Kaye's USO tours, stage appearances, especially in England, Scotland, and South Africa, and his interest in Israel. One album is devoted to 1940s-1950s publicity photos of Kaye and Fine.
  - Loose Images, 1918-1991
    Color and black and white prints, negatives, and transparencies.
    Organized as four sub-subseries: Danny Kaye, Sylvia Fine, and Family and Friends; Appearances; Production Stills; and Kaye Hobbies.
    - Danny Kaye, Sylvia Fine, and Family and Friends, 1918-1988
      Images of Kaye and Fine, their daughter, Dena Kaye, and the Kaminsky and Fine families, with the Fine family extensively represented. Many of these are studio portraits of Kaye. There are also numerous images of Kaye with friends and colleagues from all aspects of his career and personal life, as well as photographs inscribed to Kaye and Fine.
      Arranged by subject. Undated portraits of Kaye are arranged in three rough groups: early-, mid-, and late-career.
      - Kaye, Danny
        - Childhood, undated (Box-folder 502/1)
        - Portraits, Early Career, undated (Box-folder 502/2-3, 435/1, 638/1)
        - Portraits, Mid-Career, undated (Box-folder 502/4-5, 435/2-5, 622/1, 638/2, 768/5)
        - Portraits, Late Career, undated (Box-folder 502/6-7, 503/1, 435/6, 638/3)
        - Portraits, Life magazine, 1961, April 13 (Box-folder 435/7)
        - Portraits by Philippe Halsman, undated (Box-folder 503/2)
        - Portraits by Roddy McDowall, undated (Box-folder 435/8)
        - Portraits by Lotte Meitner-Graf, 1955, List of poses located in Box 622/2. (Box-folder 622/2-5, 639/1-5)
        - with Durocher, Leo, 1952, 1986, undated, Includes Jack Benny, Laraine Day, and Benay Venuta. (Box-folder 503/3)
        - with Hitzing, Holly, 1962, undated (Box-folder 503/4)
        - with King, Alexander B., undated (Box-folder 503/5)
        - with Lauder, Harry, undated (Box-folder 503/6)
        - with Libson, Nyman, undated (Box-folder 503/7)
        - with Miscellaneous People, 1944, 1960, 1975, undated, Includes Gene Bayliss and Harry Ritz. (Box-folder 503/8-9, 435/9)
        - with Performing Artists, 1940-1980, Includes Bill Allison note to Dena Kaye.; Includes Sid Field, Jerry Lewis, and Laurence Olivier. (Box-folder 503/10-11, 435/10, 622/8)
        - with Richter, Carroll, undated (Box-folder 503/12)
        - with Royalty, 1956, 1968, 1975, 1978, undated, Includes the Duchess of Kent, Prince Philip, Princess Grace, Princess Caroline, Prince Rainier, Princess Margaret, and Queen Elizabeth. (Box-folder 503/13)
        - with Swaffer, Hannen, undated (Box-folder 503/14)
        - with the Three Terpsichoreans and Other Teams, undated (Box-folder 503/15)
        - with U. S. Schoolchildren, undated (Box-folder 435/11)
        - with World Leaders, 1956-1975 undated, Includes David Ben-Gurion, Winston Churchill, Moshe Dayan, Thomas Dewey, Dwight Eisenhower, Gerald R. Ford, Hubert Humphrey, Lady Bird Johnson, Lyndon Johnson, John F. Kennedy, Henry Kissinger, Jawaharlal Nehru, Vijaya Lakshmi Pandit, Pope Paul VI, and Eleanor Roosevelt (Box-folder 504/1, 435/12)
        - with Pets, undated (Box-folder 504/2)
        - 1103 San Ysidro Drive House, undated (Box-folder 504/3)
      - Fine, Sylvia
        - Portraits, 1940-1942, 1979, undated (Box-folder 504/4, 436/1)